Ege Akman

Ege Akman's CV

Antalya

egeakmanegeakman@hotmail.com

+905427415148

Hello, I'm Ege Akman, and 16 years old. I got into programming when I was 14. I know Python, Java, HTML, CSS, Bash, and PowerShell. I actively use some Adobe CC applications such as Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Illustrator. My favorite text editor is Visual Studio Code. I am familiar with Git and GitHub. I also did create a Discord bot with Python that has features in different categories such as music, moderation, entertainment, and now we are merging our bots with a friend. Also, I'm learning C# and C++. And most importantly I love learning new things and am a fast learner.

Here are my social media accounts: GitHub: https://github.com/egeakman

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/egeakman Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/ege.akmn

Twitter: https://twitter.com/egeakmn

I hope that you hire me as an employee.

Regards...

Work Experience

Python Developer

Antalya ISAS - Antalya April 2021 to Present

I voluntarily work at Antalya ISAS as a Python Developer / Project Manager. We are making an opensource PyQt application for collecting and recording data, especially visual data, from underwater ROVs. Here is a link to the app's repository: https://repo.antalyaisas.com/tcgrida-app

Participating in FIRST Robotics Competition

First Robotics Competition - Istanbul September 2020 to Present

We call FIRST Robotics Competition the ultimate Sport for the Mind. High-school student participants call it "the hardest fun you'll ever have."

Under strict rules, limited time and resources, teams of students are challenged to raise funds, design a team "brand," hone teamwork skills, and build and program industrial-size robots to play a difficult field game against like-minded competitors. It's as close to real-world engineering as a student can get. Volunteer professional mentors lend their time and talents to guide each team. Each season ends with an exciting FIRST Championship.

Made a Discord Bot with Python

Freelance - Antalya

June 2020 to October 2020

I created a Discord bot with Python that has features in different categories such as music, moderation, entertainment.

Education

High school diploma in Computer Programming

 ${\bf Bahcesehir\ High\ School\ for\ Science\ and\ Technology\ -\ Antalya}$

August 2020 to Present

Skills

- Git (1 year)
- Java (1 year)
- Python (2 years)
- AWS (1 year)
- Azure (1 year)
- HTML5 (Less than 1 year)
- Microsoft Office (5 years)
- Google Docs (3 years)
- Robotics (4 years)
- Robot programming (4 years)
- Microsoft Windows Server (1 year)
- Windows (7 years)
- Linux (3 years)
- LAMP stack (1 year)
- Penetration testing (1 year)
- Cybersecurity (1 year)
- Adobe Photoshop (2 years)
- Adobe Premiere (1 year)
- Adobe Illustrator (Less than 1 year)
- Adobe Creative Cloud (2 years)
- Server management (1 year)
- Mac OS (1 year)
- TCP/IP (1 year)
- Computer Networking (1 year)
- Mentoring (1 year)
- English
- Leadership (3 years)

- CSS (1 year)
- Bash (2 years)
- PowerShell (2 years)

Languages

- English Fluent
- Turkish Expert

Links

https://antalyaisas.com

https://github.com/antalya-isas

https://github.com/egeakman

https://www.bkmindbenders.com

Awards

Robotex 2019 Championship Award on LEGO Sumo Category

November 2019

Robotex is an Estonian-based organization whose aim is to organize Robotex International – an annual robotics festival that brings together thousands of engineers, executives, students and families to be inspired by technology industry leaders, examine new start-ups, build robots for various challenges and learn about the latest technology innovations.